Hello friends, you all are very welcome once again to this society,
friends, if you are working in the project of
culture all i.e. my village my heritage through sugar and sea, then in such a situation,
friends, there is a very big
good news for all of you, very good news, that right now
you get clips of payment within tomorrow, then according to the
Gram Panchayat,
you can get payment up to ₹ 1000 below it,
how will you get it, what to do, where to
download that form, in what manner, what
things will be there, I will tell you in this video,
but friends, before half an hour in the video, I
bring you such new updates,
so please like and cycle the video, we will definitely
ask, please subscribe to the channel, this will give
us more encouragement, the
question is, brings videos, so let's start,
so friends, to
tell you further information about this, I have brought
you on your computer screen,
after going there, you simply have to search it on Google, sea
culture survey, okay, by
writing this much, as you will search,
you will get the link on the second or third number from the top,
really society.com's website  But
you simply have to click on CSC Culture Validation,
as if A
to Z information will appear in front of you, friend Tyagi
sir has given very important
information on this, please do like that too
and here when you scroll down,
Lucknow Commission Structure for CSE
Way is written and it has been told about the same that
how you can get the payment of ₹1000,
along with this,
information has also been given by specific tweet here,
so I had made the payment there as well, I
told you here that I am giving it, okay, so
as friends you know, the
cancer survey project is being done through C, in which
many people are
also working, within which every
Gram Panchayat and write to do it,
only a payment of ₹100 is given, but
how will you get this payment up to ₹1000, so here
friends, the complete method has been explained in this tweet, in
this way you will
get a paste of ₹1000 instead of this year  It is written here that
all the serials of Kal Service Open to All Girls In can do this type of work
and incentive of Rs.1000 will be
given for completing five years service, that is,
here you get a payment of only
₹100 for completing the survey of only one Gram Panchayat,
but if
you survey five villages, then
you will be given the full payment of ₹1000, that is, if
we think roughly, then
you will get ₹40 for every Gram Panchayat, that is,
you will get the payment as per Gram Panchayat for ₹10, okay, so I
hope friends, this information must have been
quite difficult for you and
keep one more thing in mind here that this offer, this
payment will be given only to the first 10,000 calls, that is,
if you have not yet logged in to your Kal Jab and visited the
Gram Panchayat, have
not done the work, then you must go and do it,
I have given the complete video of how to do it here, please go and
think about it.  And if you have any questions then
write in the comment box below this video, if
needed then friends I hope
you liked this video very much, if you liked the
video then please like it,
everyone understand this is uncle edition
in the video, till then Baba is needed